[{"body": [{"title": "拖拽分类", "stem": "拖一拖，把下面生活用品分为三类", "content": [{"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_1.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_3.svg"}, {"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/半裙组合_2/绿色裙子2.svg"}, {"type": "socks", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/袜子_1.svg"}, {"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/连衣裙_2.svg"}, {"type": "socks", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/袜子_2.svg"}], "type": "au-classify-drag"}], "answers": [["hat", "hat"], ["skirt", "skirt"], ["socks", "socks"]], "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-3"}, {"body": [{"title": "拖拽分类", "stem": "拖一拖，把下面生活用品分为三类", "content": [{"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_3.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg"}, {"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_1.svg"}, {"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_2.svg"}, {"type": "shoes", "src": "v2/通用/鞋靴/鞋子_3.svg"}, {"type": "shoes", "src": "v2/通用/鞋靴/鞋子_2.svg"}], "type": "au-classify-drag"}], "answers": [["hat", "hat"], ["surface", "surface"], ["shoes", "shoes"]], "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-3"}, {"body": [{"title": "拖拽分类", "stem": "拖一拖，把下面生活用品分为三类", "content": [{"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_1.svg"}, {"type": "shoes", "src": "v2/通用/鞋靴/鞋子_2.svg"}, {"type": "socks", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/袜子_2.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_3.svg"}, {"type": "shoes", "src": "v2/通用/鞋靴/鞋子_3.svg"}, {"type": "socks", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/袜子_1.svg"}], "type": "au-classify-drag"}], "answers": [["hat", "hat"], ["shoes", "shoes"], ["socks", "socks"]], "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-3"}, {"body": [{"title": "拖拽分类", "stem": "拖一拖，把下面生活用品分为三类", "content": [{"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/连衣裙_2.svg"}, {"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_2.svg"}, {"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/半裙组合_2/黄色裙子2.svg"}, {"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_4.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_5.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg"}], "type": "au-classify-drag"}], "answers": [["skirt", "skirt"], ["surface", "surface"], ["hat", "hat"]], "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-3"}, {"body": [{"title": "拖拽分类", "stem": "拖一拖，把下面生活用品分为三类", "content": [{"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/连衣裙_1.svg"}, {"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/半裙组合_2/绿色裙子2.svg"}, {"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_4.svg"}, {"type": "shoes", "src": "v2/通用/鞋靴/鞋子_3.svg"}, {"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_2.svg"}, {"type": "shoes", "src": "v2/通用/鞋靴/鞋子_2.svg"}], "type": "au-classify-drag"}], "answers": [["skirt", "skirt"], ["surface", "surface"], ["shoes", "shoes"]], "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-3"}, {"body": [{"title": "拖拽分类", "stem": "拖一拖，把下面生活用品分为三类", "content": [{"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/半裙组合_2/紫色裙子2.svg"}, {"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_3.svg"}, {"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/半裙组合_2/黄色裙子2.svg"}, {"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_4.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_2.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_5.svg"}], "type": "au-classify-drag"}], "answers": [["skirt", "skirt"], ["surface", "surface"], ["hat", "hat"]], "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-3"}, {"body": [{"title": "拖拽分类", "stem": "拖一拖，把下面生活用品分为三类", "content": [{"type": "socks", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/袜子_1.svg"}, {"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/连衣裙_1.svg"}, {"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/半裙组合_2/黄色裙子2.svg"}, {"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_1.svg"}, {"type": "socks", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/袜子_2.svg"}, {"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_2.svg"}], "type": "au-classify-drag"}], "answers": [["socks", "socks"], ["skirt", "skirt"], ["surface", "surface"]], "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-3"}, {"body": [{"title": "拖拽分类", "stem": "拖一拖，把下面生活用品分为三类", "content": [{"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_1.svg"}, {"type": "socks", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/袜子_2.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg"}, {"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/半裙组合_2/蓝色裙子2.svg"}, {"type": "socks", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/袜子_1.svg"}, {"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/半裙组合_2/绿色裙子2.svg"}], "type": "au-classify-drag"}], "answers": [["hat", "hat"], ["socks", "socks"], ["skirt", "skirt"]], "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-3"}, {"body": [{"title": "拖拽分类", "stem": "拖一拖，把下面生活用品分为三类", "content": [{"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_2.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg"}, {"type": "shoes", "src": "v2/通用/鞋靴/鞋子_2.svg"}, {"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/半裙组合_2/绿色裙子2.svg"}, {"type": "shoes", "src": "v2/通用/鞋靴/鞋子_3.svg"}, {"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/连衣裙_1.svg"}], "type": "au-classify-drag"}], "answers": [["hat", "hat"], ["shoes", "shoes"], ["skirt", "skirt"]], "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-3"}, {"body": [{"title": "拖拽分类", "stem": "拖一拖，把下面生活用品分为三类", "content": [{"type": "socks", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/袜子_2.svg"}, {"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_2.svg"}, {"type": "shoes", "src": "v2/通用/鞋靴/鞋子_2.svg"}, {"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_1.svg"}, {"type": "shoes", "src": "v2/通用/鞋靴/鞋子_1.svg"}, {"type": "socks", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/袜子_1.svg"}], "type": "au-classify-drag"}], "answers": [["socks", "socks"], ["surface", "surface"], ["shoes", "shoes"]], "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-3"}, {"body": [{"title": "拖拽分类", "stem": "拖一拖，把下面生活用品分为三类", "content": [{"type": "socks", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/袜子_2.svg"}, {"type": "shoes", "src": "v2/通用/鞋靴/鞋子_3.svg"}, {"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/短裙组合_1/短裙_1.svg"}, {"type": "shoes", "src": "v2/通用/鞋靴/鞋子_1.svg"}, {"type": "socks", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/袜子_1.svg"}, {"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/短裙组合_1/短裙_2.svg"}], "type": "au-classify-drag"}], "answers": [["socks", "socks"], ["shoes", "shoes"], ["skirt", "skirt"]], "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-3"}, {"body": [{"title": "拖拽分类", "stem": "拖一拖，把下面生活用品分为三类", "content": [{"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/连衣裙_1.svg"}, {"type": "shoes", "src": "v2/通用/鞋靴/鞋子_2.svg"}, {"type": "shoes", "src": "v2/通用/鞋靴/鞋子_3.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_5.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_2.svg"}, {"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/短裙组合_1/短裙_2.svg"}], "type": "au-classify-drag"}], "answers": [["skirt", "skirt"], ["shoes", "shoes"], ["hat", "hat"]], "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-3"}, {"body": [{"title": "拖拽分类", "stem": "拖一拖，把下面生活用品分为三类", "content": [{"type": "shoes", "src": "v2/通用/鞋靴/鞋子_2.svg"}, {"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/半裙组合_2/黄色裙子2.svg"}, {"type": "shoes", "src": "v2/通用/鞋靴/鞋子_3.svg"}, {"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_1.svg"}, {"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/短裙组合_1/短裙_1.svg"}, {"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_4.svg"}], "type": "au-classify-drag"}], "answers": [["shoes", "shoes"], ["skirt", "skirt"], ["surface", "surface"]], "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-3"}, {"body": [{"title": "拖拽分类", "stem": "拖一拖，把下面生活用品分为三类", "content": [{"type": "socks", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/袜子_2.svg"}, {"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_1.svg"}, {"type": "socks", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/袜子_1.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_1.svg"}, {"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_4.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_3.svg"}], "type": "au-classify-drag"}], "answers": [["socks", "socks"], ["surface", "surface"], ["hat", "hat"]], "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-3"}, {"body": [{"title": "拖拽分类", "stem": "拖一拖，把下面生活用品分为三类", "content": [{"type": "shoes", "src": "v2/通用/鞋靴/鞋子_2.svg"}, {"type": "socks", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/袜子_1.svg"}, {"type": "socks", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/袜子_2.svg"}, {"type": "shoes", "src": "v2/通用/鞋靴/鞋子_3.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_3.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg"}], "type": "au-classify-drag"}], "answers": [["shoes", "shoes"], ["socks", "socks"], ["hat", "hat"]], "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-3"}, {"body": [{"title": "拖拽分类", "stem": "拖一拖，把下面生活用品分为三类", "content": [{"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_5.svg"}, {"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_2.svg"}, {"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_1.svg"}, {"type": "shoes", "src": "v2/通用/鞋靴/鞋子_3.svg"}, {"type": "shoes", "src": "v2/通用/鞋靴/鞋子_1.svg"}], "type": "au-classify-drag"}], "answers": [["hat", "hat"], ["surface", "surface"], ["shoes", "shoes"]], "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-3"}]